[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "Is it going too far?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "too", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "How significant are these alleged gaffes be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "are", "these", "alleged", "gaffes", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I think there have been more unforced errors than you would expect from a presidential campaign in the final months.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "have", "been", "more", "unforced", "errors", "than", "you", "would", "expect", "from", "a", "presidential", "campaign", "in", "the", "final", "months", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "When Bill Clinton was fundraising, for example, would he often go harder on the rhetoric, thinking he was in a secure room with people that he could trust, or is this Mitt Romney's big fatal flaw, that he's been caught talking in a different way?", "question_tokens": ["When", "Bill", "Clinton", "was", "fundraising", ",", "for", "example", ",", "would", "he", "often", "go", "harder", "on", "the", "rhetoric", ",", "thinking", "he", "was", "in", "a", "secure", "room", "with", "people", "that", "he", "could", "trust", ",", "or", "is", "this", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "big", "fatal", "flaw", ",", "that", "he", "'s", "been", "caught", "talking", "in", "a", "different", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "You have just got to assume, when you're in a presidential race, that every single moment is on the record.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "just", "got", "to", "assume", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "in", "a", "presidential", "race", ",", "that", "every", "single", "moment", "is", "on", "the", "record", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "If they had somebody like that, would they be doing better in the polls?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "had", "somebody", "like", "that", ",", "would", "they", "be", "doing", "better", "in", "the", "polls", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well -- if you look back at that primary field that we were dealing with a year ago, watching in debates a year ago, there's no question with the exception perhaps of Rick Perry, who ended up imploding for other reasons, I don't think there was anybody else on that stage who could have gotten the nomination and been competitive in a presidential race.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--", "if", "you", "look", "back", "at", "that", "primary", "field", "that", "we", "were", "dealing", "with", "a", "year", "ago", ",", "watching", "in", "debates", "a", "year", "ago", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "with", "the", "exception", "perhaps", "of", "Rick", "Perry", ",", "who", "ended", "up", "imploding", "for", "other", "reasons", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "was", "anybody", "else", "on", "that", "stage", "who", "could", "have", "gotten", "the", "nomination", "and", "been", "competitive", "in", "a", "presidential", "race", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "What do you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "You got nothing left to lose.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "got", "nothing", "left", "to", "lose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "How is she doing, do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", ",", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "You know, the transplant went as well, it's transfusion, really, went as well as can be expected.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "transplant", "went", "as", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "transfusion", ",", "really", ",", "went", "as", "well", "as", "can", "be", "expected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["47 percent"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "I mean what's going on here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No, I think what he was earlier saying is that the president was polling at 47 percent, still is.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "what", "he", "was", "earlier", "saying", "is", "that", "the", "president", "was", "polling", "at", "47", "percent", ",", "still", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "You must have been incandescent, were you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "been", "incandescent", ",", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Can you do it without increasing any taxation, because from where I sit, I just don't see that is a feasible position?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "it", "without", "increasing", "any", "taxation", ",", "because", "from", "where", "I", "sit", ",", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "see", "that", "is", "a", "feasible", "position", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I think you're going to have to increase taxes, Piers, on people who are very fortunate in this society, who are very wealthy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "to", "increase", "taxes", ",", "Piers", ",", "on", "people", "who", "are", "very", "fortunate", "in", "this", "society", ",", "who", "are", "very", "wealthy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "What has he got to do to refocus, to re-galvanize and to try and get the right message over now to win this election?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "he", "got", "to", "do", "to", "refocus", ",", "to", "re-galvanize", "and", "to", "try", "and", "get", "the", "right", "message", "over", "now", "to", "win", "this", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, he needs to keep saying what he has been saying and force the press to focus on that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "needs", "to", "keep", "saying", "what", "he", "has", "been", "saying", "and", "force", "the", "press", "to", "focus", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Robert Reich, is there merit to what Grover Norquist is saying there?", "question_tokens": ["Robert", "Reich", ",", "is", "there", "merit", "to", "what", "Grover", "Norquist", "is", "saying", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "I don't think there's very much merit, if any merit at all, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "very", "much", "merit", ",", "if", "any", "merit", "at", "all", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Reich", "Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "You must be worried, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "worried", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["Soviet Union", "America", "Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Can I just -- can I just intervene here?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "just", "--", "can", "I", "just", "intervene", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "The Soviet Union was no more of a financial burden on America than Afghanistan and Iraq had been.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Soviet", "Union", "was", "no", "more", "of", "a", "financial", "burden", "on", "America", "than", "Afghanistan", "and", "Iraq", "had", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan", "Barack Obama", "George W. Bush"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "That's civil?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "civil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "The fact of the matter is the Reagan recession was very deep, but it is nothing compared to what Barack Obama inherited from George W. Bush.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "fact", "of", "the", "matter", "is", "the", "Reagan", "recession", "was", "very", "deep", ",", "but", "it", "is", "nothing", "compared", "to", "what", "Barack", "Obama", "inherited", "from", "George", "W.", "Bush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Has any president in the history of the United States ever handed a bigger financial crisis over to the guy that followed him than George Bush did?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "any", "president", "in", "the", "history", "of", "the", "United", "States", "ever", "handed", "a", "bigger", "financial", "crisis", "over", "to", "the", "guy", "that", "followed", "him", "than", "George", "Bush", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "Well, if you look at --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Bush"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herbert Hoover"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Who?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Herbert Hoover.", "answer_tokens": ["Herbert", "Hoover", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hoover"], "PERCENT": ["75 percent"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Are you saying that FDR was the same as Herbert Hoover?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "saying", "that", "FDR", "was", "the", "same", "as", "Herbert", "Hoover", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Well, he did -- Hoover took tax rates up to 75 percent from 25.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "did", "--", "Hoover", "took", "tax", "rates", "up", "to", "75", "percent", "from", "25", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FDR"], "PERSON": ["Herbert Hoover"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Isn't that a very similar position to what we're now seeing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "a", "very", "similar", "position", "to", "what", "we", "'re", "now", "seeing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "It's not, because the president just gave a speech about how the American people demanded Obamacare.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", ",", "because", "the", "president", "just", "gave", "a", "speech", "about", "how", "the", "American", "people", "demanded", "Obamacare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Not much of it good.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "much", "of", "it", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How much credence should we be giving it, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "credence", "should", "we", "be", "giving", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "As to that part of it, plenty.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "to", "that", "part", "of", "it", ",", "plenty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Defense Department"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "I wouldn't even have been aware of him being released?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "even", "have", "been", "aware", "of", "him", "being", "released", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "No, he was in custody of the Defense Department.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "was", "in", "custody", "of", "the", "Defense", "Department", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "It is just a collection of terrorist cells around the world?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "just", "a", "collection", "of", "terrorist", "cells", "around", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Well, it's essentially a franchise.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "essentially", "a", "franchise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Do you think that is plausible?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "plausible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Sure, it's plausible.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "it", "'s", "plausible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Department"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Do you think there's any danger that he will be released at any stage, in any capacity?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "danger", "that", "he", "will", "be", "released", "at", "any", "stage", ",", "in", "any", "capacity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "UKASEY: I don't take a denial from the Justice Department as dispositive.", "answer_tokens": ["UKASEY", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "take", "a", "denial", "from", "the", "Justice", "Department", "as", "dispositive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Final point I would make, do you believe from what we have seen in the last week, then, that America is once again under attack from al Qaeda?", "question_tokens": ["Final", "point", "I", "would", "make", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "from", "what", "we", "have", "seen", "in", "the", "last", "week", ",", "then", ",", "that", "America", "is", "once", "again", "under", "attack", "from", "al", "Qaeda", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "America has always been under attack from al Qaeda.", "answer_tokens": ["America", "has", "always", "been", "under", "attack", "from", "al", "Qaeda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["17.5 billion dollars"]}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "I suppose the obvious question is how much can we expect to recover in the end?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "the", "obvious", "question", "is", "how", "much", "can", "we", "expect", "to", "recover", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "ICARD: Well, we'd like to think that we can recover all the 17.5 billion dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["ICARD", ":", "Well", ",", "we", "'d", "like", "to", "think", "that", "we", "can", "recover", "all", "the", "17.5", "billion", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Is that likely?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "likely", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "It depends on litigation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", "litigation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Are you pleasantly encouraged by how far you've come so far?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "pleasantly", "encouraged", "by", "how", "far", "you", "'ve", "come", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Oh, absolutely, because we started at zero.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", ",", "because", "we", "started", "at", "zero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Stephen, has Bernie Madoff been helpful at all in this process?", "question_tokens": ["Stephen", ",", "has", "Bernie", "Madoff", "been", "helpful", "at", "all", "in", "this", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I would say no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stephen", "Bernie Madoff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "That's correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "CC", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "How would you categorize him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "categorize", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "ICARD: I really haven't thought about characterizing him at this point, because our efforts and our focus has been to go out and recover what we can, as much as we can, as quickly as we can, for the people for whom we are trying to get the best recoveries and best distribution.", "answer_tokens": ["ICARD", ":", "I", "really", "have", "n't", "thought", "about", "characterizing", "him", "at", "this", "point", ",", "because", "our", "efforts", "and", "our", "focus", "has", "been", "to", "go", "out", "and", "recover", "what", "we", "can", ",", "as", "much", "as", "we", "can", ",", "as", "quickly", "as", "we", "can", ",", "for", "the", "people", "for", "whom", "we", "are", "trying", "to", "get", "the", "best", "recoveries", "and", "best", "distribution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "This was the biggest Ponzi scheme in American history, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "the", "biggest", "Ponzi", "scheme", "in", "American", "history", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "If you were to succeed in recovering the money, it would be the biggest recovery of its type that we would have ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "to", "succeed", "in", "recovering", "the", "money", ",", "it", "would", "be", "the", "biggest", "recovery", "of", "its", "type", "that", "we", "would", "have", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 554, "question": "He's pretty despicable human being, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "pretty", "despicable", "human", "being", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I don't know that I would go that far, because, you know --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "I", "would", "go", "that", "far", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Is that the maxim?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "maxim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Well, that is true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]